Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series V. Within the College, 1951-1979
  - Students Correspondence — General, 1976-1978 (Folder 63.12)
  - Student — A, 1973-1977 (Folder 63.13)
  - Student — B, 1972-1978 (Folder 63.14)
  - Student — C, 1972-1977 (Folder 63.15)
  - Student — D, 1975-1978 (Folder 63.16)
  - Student — E, 1974-1975 (Folder 63.17)
  - Student — F, 1976-1978 (Folder 63.18)
  - Student — G, 1974-1977 (Folder 63.19)
  - Student — H, 1974-1977 (Folder 63.20)
  - Student — J, 1973 (Folder 63.21)
  - Student — K, 1975-1978 (Folder 63.22)
  - Student — L, 1975-1978 (Folder 63.23)
  - Student — M, 1976-1978 (Folder 63.24)
  - Student — N, 1973-1977 (Folder 63.25)
  - Student — O, 1973-1976 (Folder 63.26)
  - Student — P, 1973-1977 (Folder 63.27)
  - Student — R, 1974-1977 (Folder 63.28)
  - Student — S, 1974-1977 (Folder 63.29)
  - Student — T, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.30)
  - Student — U, 1975 (Folder 63.31)
  - Student — V, 1976 (Folder 63.32)
  - Student — W, 1973-1977 (Folder 63.33)
  - Student — X-Y-Z, 1975-1977 (Folder 63.34)
  - Student Newspaper — Vassar Chronicle, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.35)
  - Student Senate, 1975-1977 (Folder 63.36)
  - Student Government Association (SGA), 1975-1977 (Folder 63.37)
  - Student Newspaper — The Miscellany News, 1975-1977 (Folder 63.38)
  - Student Radio Station — WVKR, 1977-1978 (Folder 63.39)
  - T — General, 1976-1978 (Folder 63.40)
  - Tuition Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.41)
  - U — General Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Folder 63.42)
  - V — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.43)
  - W — General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.44)
  - Women Presidents’ Meeting, 1977 (Folder 63.45)
  - X-Y-Z — General Correspondence, (empty) (Folder 63.46)
  - Affirmative Action, 1976-1977 (Folder 63.47)
  - Affirmative Action, 1974-1976 (Folder 63.48)
  - Faculty Meeting (Current), 1970-1971 (Folder 63.49)
  - Faculty Material re Grad Center, 1970 (Folder 63.50)
  - Faculty Ad Hoc Committee, 1975 (Folder 63.51)
  - Faculty Salary Freeze — Chronological File, 1975-1976 (Folder 63.52)
  - Tenure and Other Decisions, 1974-1975 (Folder 63.53)
  - Faculty Committees, 1974-1975 (Folder 63.54)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1971 Apr-May (Folder 63.55)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Folder 63.56)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Folder 63.57)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1973 (Folder 64.1)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1972-1973 (Folder 64.2)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1973-1974 (Folder 64.3)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1976-1977 (Folder 64.4)
  - Education Reports, 1969-1970 (Folder 64.5)
  - Audubon Birds, 1964-1969 (Folder 64.6)
  - Havelock Speech to Faculty on Admissions, 1975 (Folder 64.7)
  - Simpson — Miscellaneous Letters, 1973-1976 (Folder 64.8)
  - Simpson Letters, 1976-1977 (Folder 64.9)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Folder 64.10)
  - Academic Freedom, 1953 (Folder 64.11)
  - Administrative Growth, 1976-1977 (Folder 64.12)
  - Applications (Miscellaneous) — F-O, 1970-1977 (Folder 64.13)
  - Applications (Miscellaneous) — P-Z, 1970-1976 (Folder 64.14)
  - Black Students, 1975-1977 (Folder 64.15)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1970-1977 (Folder 64.16)
  - Letters to Mr. Simpson from Velma, 1975-1977 (Folder 64.17)
  - E-P-E 15-Minute Reports, 1973-1974 (Folder 64.18)
  - New York State Education Department, 1968-1971 (Folder 64.19)
  - New York State Education Department, 1971-1972 (Folder 64.20)
  - New York State Education Department, 1972-1974 (Folder 64.21)
  - New York State Education Department, 1974-1975 (Folder 64.22)
  - New York State Education Department, 1975-1976 (Folder 64.23)
  - New York State Education Department, 1976-1977 (Folder 64.24)
  - Senior Staff, 1976-1977 (Folder 64.25)
  - Senior Staff, 1975-1976 (Folder 64.26)
  - Seven College Conference, 1974 (Folder 64.27)
  - Seven College Conference, 1973-1974 (Folder 64.28)
  - Seven College Conference, 1971-1973 (Folder 64.29)
  - Mr. Simpson’s notes to himself, 1975-1976 (Folder 64.30)
  - Students General, 1968-1977 (Folder 64.31)
  - Students Mail (Recommendations), 1975 (Folder 64.32)
- Series VI. Associations, 1958-1977
  - American Association of University Professors, 1964-1966 (Folder 65.1)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1966-1967 (Folder 65.2)
  - Association of American Colleges — Dean Keeton’s Study: Future of Liberal Arts Colleges, 1965-1966 (Folder 65.3)
  - Association of American Colleges – Commission on Liberal Learning, 1964-1966 (Folder 65.4)
  - Association of American Colleges — Commission on Liberal Learning, 1966-1967 (Folder 65.5)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1964-1966 (Folder 65.6)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of N.Y., 1967 (Folder 65.7)
  - American Council on Education — Board of Directors, 1966-1967 (Folder 65.8)
  - American Council on Education — Board of Directors Meeting, 1967 May-Jun (Folder 65.9)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1965-1967 (Folder 65.10)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1964-1966 (Folder 65.11)
  - American Council on Education — Panel on Academic Freedom (Students), 1964-1965 (Folder 65.12)
  - American Council on Education — Commission on Academic Affairs, 1964-1965 (Folder 65.13)
  - American Council on Education — Commission on Plans and objectives, 1966-1967 (Folder 65.14)
  - American Council on Education, 1964-1966 (Folder 65.15)
  - American Council on Education, 1966-1967 (Folder 65.16)
  - Seven College Conference, 1964-1965 (Folder 65.17)
  - Seven College Conference, 1965-1967 (Folder 65.18)
  - A Profile of Vassar College 1954-1974, 1964 (Folder 65.19)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1966-1967 (Folder 65.20)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1959-1967 (Folder 65.21)
  - Danforth Foundation — Study Group, 1964-1965 (Folder 65.22)
  - Empire State Foundation of Independent Liberal Arts Colleges, 1964-1965 (Folder 65.23)
  - Empire State Foundation, 1965-1966 (Folder 65.24)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1966 Dec 12 (Folder 65.25)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1967 Apr 3 (Folder 65.26)
  - Ford Foundation, 1965-1967 (Folder 65.27)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1958-1966 (Folder 65.28)
  - National Scholarship and Fund for Negro Students, 1962-1966 (Folder 65.29)
  - Women’s College Board of Chicago, 1964-1967 (Folder 65.30)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation, 1965-1967 (Folder 65.31)
  - American Antiquarian Society, 1965-1966 (Folder 65.32)
  - American Historical Association, 1964-1965 (Folder 65.33)
  - Associated College of Mid-Hudson Area — Candidates for Director, 1968-1969 (Folder 65.34)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1964-1965 (Folder 66.1)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1965-1966 (Folder 66.2)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1967-1969 (Folder 66.3)
  - Mid-Hudson College Association — Minutes of Meetings, 1962-1966 (Folder 66.4)
  - Conference on British Studies, 1965-1968 (Folder 66.5)
  - Coordinating Council of Office of Foreign Area Studies, 1967-1968 (Folder 66.6)
  - Coordinating Council of Office of Foreign Area Studies, 1965-1966 (Folder 66.7)
  - Dutchess Area Community Chest, 1965-1969 (Folder 66.8)
  - State Advisory Committee to the Guidance Centers for Women, 1966-1967 (Folder 66.9)
  - State Advisory Committee to the Guidance Centers for Women, 1967-1968 (Folder 66.10)
  - Historical Society of Rockland County, 1968 (Folder 66.11)
  - Hudson Valley Philharmonic Society, 1966-1969 (Folder 66.12)
  - Maria Mitchell Association, 1965-1967 (Folder 66.13)
  - Marine Midland National Bank, 1967-1969 (Folder 66.14)
  - Marine Midland National Bank, 1965-1966 (Folder 66.15)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1965-1966 (Folder 66.16)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1966-1967 (Folder 66.17)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1967-1968 (Folder 66.18)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1968-1969 (Folder 66.19)
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students, 1965-1967 (Folder 66.20)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1963-1967 (Folder 66.21)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School — Agreement and Lease, 1963-1969 (Folder 66.22)
  - Regional Plan Association — Morris Crawford, Chairman, 1964-1967 (Folder 66.23)
  - Regional Plan Association — Morris Crawford, Chairman, 1966-1968 (Folder 66.24)
  - Tobe-Coburn School for Fashion Careers, 1964-1969 (Folder 66.25)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1966-1968 (Folder 66.26)
  - Colonial Williamsburg — Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1967-1968 (Folder 67.1)
  - Colonial Williamsburg — Operations, 1967-1968 (Folder 67.2)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1965-1971; (9 folders) (Folder 67.3 – 67.11)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1966-1970; (21 folders) (Folder 68.1 – 68.21)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1970-1971 (Folder 68.22)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1968-1970 (Folder 68.23)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1967-1968 (Folder 68.24)
  - American Association of University Women, 1967-1969 (Folder 68.25)
  - American Council on Education, 1967-1971; (9 folders) (Folder 68.26 – 68.34)
  - American Council on Education, 1967-1970; (3 folders) (Folder 69.1 – 69.3)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1968-1969 (Folder 69.4)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1967-1969 (Folder 69.5)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1967-1969 (Folder 69.6)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1968-1971 (Folder 69.7)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1968-1969 (Folder 69.8)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1967-1969 (Folder 69.9)
  - Middle States Association, 1969-1970 (Folder 69.10)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968-1970 (Folder 69.11)
  - Institute of International Education, 1967-1970 (Folder 69.12)
  - Evaluation of Vassar College, 1958 Mar (Folder 69.13)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1969 (Folder 69.14)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1967-1969 (Folder 69.15)
  - Northeast Conference on Teaching of Foreign Languages, 1967 (Folder 69.16)
  - Woman’s College Board of Chicago, 1967-1970 (Folder 69.17)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation, 1967-1970 (Folder 69.18)
  - Seven College Conference, 1967-1968 (Folder 69.19)
  - Seven College Conference, 1968-1969 (Folder 69.20)
  - Seven College Conference, 1969-1970 (Folder 69.21)
  - Seven College Conference, 1970-1971 (Folder 69.22)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1965-1967 (Folder 69.23)
  - Association of Colleges and universities of the State of New York, 1969-1971 (Folder 69.24)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1968-1971 (Folder 69.25)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1969-1971 (Folder 69.26)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1968-1971 (Folder 69.27)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1968-1971 (Folder 69.28)
  - Education Abstracts, 1966-1968 (Folder 69.29)
  - Ford Foundation, 1967-1970 (Folder 69.30)
  - ACMHA (Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area) — Urban Center, 1969 (Folder 69.31)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1969-1971 (Folder 70.1)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1970-1971 (Folder 70.2)
  - Catalyst, 1969-1971 (Folder 70.3)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1968-1971; (6 folders) (Folder 70.4 – 70.9)
  - Conference on British Studies, 1970 (Folder 70.10)
  - Dutchess Area Community Chest, 1969-1970 (Folder 70.11)
  - Dutchess County Landmarks Association, 1969-1970 (Folder 70.12)
  - Hudson Valley Philharmonic Society, 1969-1971 (Folder 70.13)
  - Maria Mitchell Association, 1970 (Folder 70.14)
  - Marine Midland National Bank, 1969-1971 (Folder 70.15)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1969-1970 (Folder 70.16)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1970-1971 (Folder 70.17)
  - National Organization for Women, 1970 (Folder 71.1)
  - Population Crisis Committee, 1970 (Folder 71.2)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1969-1971 (Folder 71.3)
  - Presidential Task Force — Meeting, 1969 Sep (Folder 71.4)
  - Presidential Task Force, 1970-1971 (Folder 71.5)
  - Presidential Task Force, 1969-1970 (Folder 71.6)
  - Recommendations and Requests not fulfilled, 1969-1971 (Folder 71.7)
  - Recommendations, 1969-1971 (Folder 71.8)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1969 (Folder 71.9)
  - Tobe-Coburn School for Fashion Careers, 1969-1971 (Folder 71.10)
  - American Council on Education, 1971-1975 (Folder 71.11)
  - American Council on Education — Commission on Academic Affairs, 1975-1976 (Folder 71.12)
  - American Council on Education — Commission on Academic Affairs, 1974-1975 (Folder 71.13)
  - Commission on Academic Affairs — ACE Meeting, 1975 Mar (Folder 71.14)
  - Catalyst, 1971-1972 (Folder 71.15)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1971-1972 (Folder 71.16)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1972-1973 (Folder 71.17)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1973-1974 (Folder 71.18)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Meeting, 1973 Nov (Folder 71.19)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1974-1975 (Folder 72.1)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities of the State of New York (CICU), 1971-1975; (7 folders) (Folder 72.2 – 72.8)
  - Association of Colleges and universities of the State of New York — (VC) Statewide Master Plan, 1972 (Folder 72.9)
  - Association of Colleges and universities of the State of New York — Statewide Master Plan, 1971-1972 (Folder 72.10)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1971-1972 (Folder 72.11)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1972-1973 (Folder 72.12)
  - American Council on Education — Commission on Academic Affairs, 1976 (Folder 72.13)
  - Marine Midland National Bank, 1975-1976 (Folder 72.14)
  - Marine Midland National Bank, 1971-1975 (Folder 72.15)
  - Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1971-1977; (6 folders) (Folder 72.16 – 72.21)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1971 (Folder 72.22)
  - The Eleanor Roosevelt Institute, 1973-1975 (Folder 72.23)
  - Tobe Coburn School for Fashion Careers, 1972-1975 (Folder 72.24)
  - American Council on Education, 1975-1975 (Folder 73.1)
  - American Council on Education, 1974-1975 (Folder 73.2)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1971-1972 (Folder 73.3)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1972-1973 (Folder 73.4)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1973-1974 (Folder 73.5)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1974-1975 (Folder 73.6)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1971-1975 (Folder 73.7)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1971-1975 (Folder 73.8)
  - Association of Colleges and universities of the State of New York, 1971-1976 (Folder 73.9)
  - Association of Governing Boards, 1973 (Folder 73.10)
  - Association of Governing Boards, 1974-1975 (Folder 73.11)
  - Commission on Academic Tenure, 1971 (Folder 73.12)
  - The Council for the Advancement of Small Colleges (CASC), 1975 (Folder 73.13)
  - Council for Financial Aid for Education, 1975 (Folder 73.14)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1971-1976 (Folder 73.15)
- Series VII. Without the College, 1962-1976
  - Legislation — State and Federal, 1964-1966 (Folder 73.16)
  - National Science Foundation, 1962-1976 (Folder 73.17)
  - Civil Rights and Vietnam, 1963-1972 (Folder 73.18)
  - State Aid for Private Education, 1968 (Folder 73.19)
  - Without College — A, 1968-1976 (Folder 73.20)
  - Without College — B, 1968-1976 (Folder 73.21)
  - Without College — C, 1968-1976 (Folder 73.22)
  - Without College — D, 1968-1976 (Folder 73.23)
  - Without College — E, 1968-1975 (Folder 73.24)
  - Without College — F, 1968-1976 (Folder 73.25)
  - Without College — G, 1968-1976 (Folder 73.26)
  - Without College — H, 1868-1976 (Folder 73.27)
  - Without College — I, 1969-1976 (Folder 73.28)
  - IBM (Folder 73.29)
  - Without College — J, 1969-1975 (Folder 73.30)
  - Without College — K, 1969-1976 (Folder 73.31)
  - Without College — L, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.1)
  - Without College — M, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.2)
  - Without College — N, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.3)
  - Without College — O, 1971-1975 (Folder 74.4)
  - Without College — P, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.5)
  - Without College — Q, 1975 (Folder 74.6)
  - Without College — R, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.7)
  - Without College — S, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.8)
  - Without College — T, 1969-1973 (Folder 74.9)
  - Without College — U, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.10)
  - Without College — V, 1975 (Folder 74.11)
  - Without College — W, 1965-1976 (Folder 74.12)
  - Without College — X-Y-Z, 1968-1976 (Folder 74.13)
  - Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency, 1970-1972 (Folder 74.14)
- Series VIII. Colleges and Universities, 1961-1977
  - Amherst College, 1965-1968 (Folder 74.15)
  - Barnard College, 1966-1968 (Folder 74.16)
  - Bard College, 1968 (Folder 74.17)
  - Bennett College, 1962-1968 (Folder 74.18)
  - Bennington College, 1964 (Folder 74.19)
  - Boston University, 1965-1966 (Folder 74.20)
  - Bowdoin College, 1967 (Folder 74.21)
  - Bradford junior College, 1966 (Folder 74.22)
  - Brandeis University, 1964, 1968 (Folder 74.23)
  - Briarcliff College, 1964-1967 (Folder 74.24)
  - The Bookings Institution, 1962, 1965 (Folder 74.25)
  - Brown University, 1962-1966 (Folder 74.26)
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1963 (Folder 74.27)
  - Bucknell University, 1964-1965 (Folder 74.28)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1966-1967 (Folder 74.29)
  - California State College at San Bernardino, 1967 (Folder 74.30)
  - Carleton College, 1965-1967 (Folder 74.31)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1964-1965 (Folder 74.32)
  - Case Western Reserve University, 1967-1968 (Folder 74.33)
  - Cedar Crest College, 1967 (Folder 74.34)
  - Chapman College, 1967 (Folder 74.35)
  - Chatman College, 1967 (Folder 74.36)
  - City University of New York, 1964 (Folder 74.37)
  - Colby Junior College, 1965 (Folder 74.38)
  - Colgate University, 1966-1968 (Folder 74.39)
  - College of Saint Teresa, 1966 (Folder 74.40)
  - Colorado Woman’s College, 1967 (Folder 74.41)
  - Columbia University, 1965-1968 (Folder 74.42)
  - Cornell University, 1963-1967 (Folder 74.43)
  - Douglass College, 1967-1968 (Folder 74.44)
  - Drake University, 1964 (Folder 74.45)
  - Duke University, 1966 (Folder 74.46)
  - Dutchess Community College, 1964-1966 (Folder 74.47)
  - Eisenhower College, 1965-1967 (Folder 74.48)
  - Elmira College, 1967 (Folder 74.49)
  - Franklin and Marshall, 1966-1967 (Folder 74.50)
  - Goucher College, 1964-1968 (Folder 74.51)
  - Hamilton College, 1963-1968 (Folder 74.52)
  - Harpur College, 1965 (Folder 74.53)
  - Harrisburg Area Community College, 1964 (Folder 74.54)
  - Hartwick College, 1964-1965 (Folder 74.55)
  - Harvard University, 1964-1968 (Folder 74.56)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1967 (Folder 74.57)
  - Hollins College, 1967 (Folder 74.58)
  - Hunter College, 1966 (Folder 74.59)
  - Jersey City State College, 1964-1965 (Folder 74.60)
  - Kent State University, 1964 (Folder 74.61)
  - Keuka College, 1966 (Folder 74.62)
  - Lake Forest College, 1964-1965 (Folder 74.63)
  - Lehigh University, 1965 (Folder 74.64)
  - Long Island University, 1967 (Folder 74.65)
  - Loretto Heights College, 1966 (Folder 74.66)
  - Mackinac College, 1966 (Folder 74.67)
  - ManhattanVille College of the Sacred Heart, 1966 (Folder 74.68)
  - Marist College, 1965-1966 (Folder 74.69)
  - Marymount Manhattan College, 1967 (Folder 74.70)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965-1966 (Folder 74.71)
  - Meredith College, 1967 (Folder 74.72)
  - Mills College, 1967 (Folder 74.73)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1963-1967 (Folder 74.74)
  - National College of Education, 1965 (Folder 74.75)
  - New Paltz, New York (State Teachers College), 1963-1968 (Folder 74.76)
  - New York State College for Teachers — Albany, new York, 1967 (Folder 74.77)
  - New York University, 1961-1967 (Folder 74.78)
  - Oberlin College, 1965 (Folder 74.79)
  - Occidental College, 1965 (Folder 74.80)
  - Ohio State University, 1966-1967 (Folder 74.81)
  - Pace College, 1966-1967 (Folder 74.82)
  - Pierce College, 1966 (Folder 74.83)
  - Pine Manor Junior College, 1965-1967 (Folder 74.84)
  - Princeton University, 1963-1968 (Folder 74.85)
  - Radcliffe College, 1961-1968 (Folder 74.86)
  - Randolph-Macon Woman’s College, 1965-1968 (Folder 74.87)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1963-1967 (Folder 74.88)
  - Russell Sage College, 1968 (Folder 74.89)
  - Rutgers University, 1966 (Folder 74.90)
  - Saint John’s College, 1966 (Folder 74.91)
  - St. John’s University, 1966 (Folder 74.92)
  - San Jose State College, 1967 (Folder 74.93)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1965-1966 (Folder 74.94)
  - Shimer College, 1968 (Folder 74.95)
  - Skidmore College, 1963-1968 (Folder 74.96)
  - Smith College, 1964-1968 (Folder 74.97)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1967 (Folder 74.98)
  - Spellman College, 1962, 1966 (Folder 74.99)
  - Stanford University, 1965 (Folder 74.100)
  - Sweet Briar College, 1964 (Folder 74.101)
  - Syracuse University, 1963-1967 (Folder 74.102)
  - Talladega College, 1962-1964 (Folder 74.103)
  - Tulane University, 1966-1967 (Folder 74.104)
  - Tuskegee Institute, 1968 (Folder 74.105)
  - Union College, 1965-1967 (Folder 75.1)
  - United States Military Academy, 1964-1966 (Folder 75.2)
  - United States Naval Academy, 1966 (Folder 75.3)
  - University of Bridgeport, 1963 (Folder 75.4)
  - University of Buffalo, 1967 (Folder 75.5)
  - University of California, 1964-1967 (Folder 75.6)
  - University of Chicago, 1962-1968 (Folder 75.7)
  - University of Connecticut, 1964 (Folder 75.8)
  - University of Denver, 1961 (Folder 75.9)
  - University of Kentucky, 1964 (Folder 75.10)
  - University of Massachusetts, 1965 (Folder 75.11)
  - University of Michigan, 1963-1967 (Folder 75.12)
  - University of Minnesota, 1967 (Folder 75.13)
  - University of New Hampshire, 1966 (Folder 75.14)
  - University of the State of New York Center for Science and Technology, 1963 (Folder 75.15)
  - University of North Carolina, 1965 (Folder 75.16)
  - University of Oklahoma, 1965 (Folder 75.17)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1963-1964 (Folder 75.18)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1966-1968 (Folder 75.19)
  - University of Rochester, 1962-1965 (Folder 75.20)
  - University of the State of New York, 1964 (Folder 75.21)
  - University of the State of New York, 1964-1965 (Folder 75.22)
  - University of the State of New York, 1965-1966 (Folder 75.23)
  - University of the State of New York, 1966-1967 (Folder 75.24)
  - University of the State of New York, 1967-1968 (Folder 75.25)
  - University of the State of New York, 1966-1968 (Folder 75.26)
  - University of Texas, 1965 (Folder 75.27)
  - University of Toronto, 1964, 1967 (Folder 75.28)
  - University of Virginia, 1968 (Folder 75.29)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1965-1966 (Folder 75.30)
  - Vermont University, 1964 (Folder 75.31)
  - Wagner College, 1965 (Folder 75.32)
  - Washington University (St. Louis, Missouri), 1966 (Folder 75.33)
  - Wayne University, 1961, 1965 (Folder 75.34)
  - Wellesley College, 1961-1966 (Folder 75.35)
  - Wells College, 1964-1965 (Folder 75.36)
  - Wesleyan University, 1962-1968 (Folder 75.37)
  - State University at Westbury, 1967-1968 (Folder 75.38)
  - Western Washington State College, 1967 (Folder 75.39)
  - Wheaton College, 1965-1968 (Folder 75.40)
  - Wilberforce University, 1966-1967 (Folder 75.41)
  - Yale University, 1962-1968 (Folder 75.42)
  - Yeshiva University, 1965 (Folder 75.43)
  - Binghamton, SUNY at, 1975 (Folder 75.44)
  - Katherine Branson School, 1971-1975 (Folder 75.45)
  - Buffalo, SUNY at, 1969-1974 (Folder 75.46)
  - Taft School, 1964-1965 (Folder 75.47)
  - Swarthmore College, 1969-1973 (Folder 75.48)
  - Amherst College, 1969-1976 (Folder 75.49)
  - Bennington College, 1976 (Folder 75.50)
  - Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute, 1967-1969 (Folder 75.51)
  - Chicago, University of, 1968-1976 (Folder 75.52)
  - Columbia University, 1969-1977 (Folder 75.53)